<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Happy Birthday!!</title>
    <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Happy Birthday!!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 12:53:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 12:53:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>As you&amp;rsquo;ve already pieced together by now, your gifts this year are related to your summer To-Do list :)
The gifts (posts) on this site are selected items from your original To-Do list along my attempt at helping you complete them. Some are silly, others are more genuine. The gifts can be opened in any order. Use the Homepage button on the upper banner to return to the main page; alternatively, you can navigate via the post thumbnails at the bottom of each page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Inbox Zero</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 11:52:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift1/</guid>
      <description>☑ Create a new google account for mail   This is the one we talked about in the car! It was agreed that you NEED a new email. One&amp;rsquo;s been made for ya now. You can use the old one for all the shady web newsletters you can sign up for!
  Credentials: Email: [removed] Password: [removed]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cook the Books</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:53:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift3/</guid>
      <description>☑ Read a cookbook like Salt Fat Acid Heat, or watch its Netflix special   When you mentioned this item a while ago, you got me interested in the book too. We can watch the Netflix series if you want (still available?), but now you have the book to go with it. It&amp;rsquo;s been delivered to my house in Auburn.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the receipt!   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, put it on my Banana Republic Platinum Plus Preferred Deluxe Card please</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 09:56:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift2/</guid>
      <description>☑ Begin search for new credit card   It&amp;rsquo;s time. And you deserve better than fast-fashion finances. You now have NerdWallet account set up and ready to be used for credit card comparison. Here&amp;rsquo;s an article from them to get you started. I recommend a cash-back card as you don&amp;rsquo;t strike me as a &amp;ldquo;perks&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;travel&amp;rdquo; rewards kinda gal. NerdWallet also offers new featurs now like credit score tracking and a budgeting manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiscally Conservative But, Like, Socially Liberal for Sure</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 09:55:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift6/</guid>
      <description>Ok this one&amp;rsquo;s kind of a joke, but now that you&amp;rsquo;re a DC Consultant, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be best that you start dressing like one.
You are now the proud owner of a&amp;hellip; (thrifted) Columbia business vest!!! After you put it on, please teach me about stocks bro.
  (Yes it&amp;rsquo;s my old one, but it&amp;rsquo;s yours now)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Hate Hackers</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 08:53:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift4/</guid>
      <description>☑ Organize and update compromised passwords   The above is one of my favorite xkcd comics. It&amp;rsquo;s a humorous insight into the modern dilemma of keeping track of your passwords.
Introducing to you Bitwarden! It&amp;rsquo;s a free, open source password management service. Store web credentials in their &amp;ldquo;vault&amp;rdquo;, which is protected by one Master password. The application can be accessed via mobile or on a desktop app and used in the background for whatever you&amp;rsquo;re doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Don&#39;t Have the Moxie</title>
      <link>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 07:53:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//justinoeuf.github.io/happy_birthday_maya/post/gift5/</guid>
      <description>☑ Look into Glamnetics   LOL. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot about magnetic lashes this week. Not sure what conversation we had that resulted in this being on the list, but here it is! You have one set of lashes + liner combo to experiment with. Apparently, Glamnetics magnetic lashes are the best for Asian eyes?
This post&amp;rsquo;s title comes from the fact that there is a hot debate on the internet about who has the better magnetic liner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
